NAA Committee Files 6205
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Casselman, James D. Towne, J.E. Abel and George Hill v. Idaho., 1949 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  On Petition for Writs of Certiorari to the Supreme Court of the State of Idaho. U.S. Supreme Court 1949. Arthur J. Goldberg.
- Charles Dowd Box Co. v. Courtney, et.al., 1961 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Brief for Respondents. U.S. Supreme Court 1961. David E. Feller, et.al.
- Circuit City v Saint Clair Adams. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Brief Amicus Curiae of the National Academy of Arbitrators in Support of the Petition. U.S. Supreme Court. Washington, D.C.: Wilson-Epes, n.d. David E. Feller
- Circuit City v. Saint Clair Adams. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Brief Amicus Curiae of the National Academy of Arbitrators in Support of the Respondent. U.S. Supreme Court. Washington, D.C.: Wilson-Epes, n.d. David E. Feller and John Kagel.
- Civil Rights Act of 1964. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Public Law 88-352. 88th Congress, H.R. 7152. July 2, 1964
- Colella v. U.S., 1964 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Petition for a Writ of Certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the First Circuit. U.S. Supreme Court 1965. Albert L. Goldman, David E. Feller, and Jerry D. Anker.
- Eastern Associated Coal v. United Mine Workers, Local 1503. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Brief Amicus Curiae of the National Academy of Arbitrators in Support of Respondents. U.S. Supreme Court. Washington, D.C.: Wilson-Epes, n.d. Theodore J. St. Antoine, David E. Feller, and John Kagel.
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1994 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  Amicus Curiae Brief of Council of University of California Faculty Association in Support of Plaintiffs/Respondents. California Court of Appeal, First Appellate District, Division Two. David E. Feller and Robert C. Post. [1994].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1994 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Appellants' Brief in Reply to Amicus Curiae Brief of Council of University of California Faculty Associations. California Court of Appeal, First Appellate District, Division Two. Kennedy P. Richardson, Mark Palley, and Willis F. McComas. [1994].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Application for Leave to Appear Pro Hac Vice. California State Supreme Court. David E. Feller. [1995].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  Application for Leave to File Amici Curiae Brief and Amici Curiae Brief on Behalf of Defendants and Respondents. California State Supreme Court. Curtis A. Cole and Michelle Logan-Stern. Lawyers Brief Service, Appellate Brief Printers. [1996].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  Application for Leave to File Amicus Curiae Brief and Amicus Curiae Brief of California Chamber of Commerce in Support of Defendants and Appellants. California State Supreme Court. Gerald Z. Marer, Esq., Kenneth J. Philpot, Esq. [1996].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  Application for Leave to File Amicus Curiae Brief and Amicus Curiae Brief of Council of University of California Faculty Associations in Support of Petitioners. California State Supreme Court. David E. Feller. [1995].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  Application for Leave to File Amicus Curiae Brief and Amicus Curiae Brief on Behalf of Defendants and Respondents. California State Supreme Court. Kenneth R. Zuetel, Jr. and Victoria K. Torigian. [1996].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  Application for Leave to File Amicus Curiae Brief. California Court of Appeal, First Appellate District, Division Two. David E. Feller. [1995].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  Defendants' Answer to Amicus Curiae Brief of Council of University of California Faculty Associations. California State Supreme Court. Kennedy P. Richardson, Mark Palley, and Willis F. McComas. [1996] and Medical Malpractice: Alternatives to Litigation. United States General Accounting Office, Report to Congressional Committees. [1992].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  Defendants' Brief on the Merits. California State Supreme Court. Kennedy P. Richardson, Mark Palley, and Willis F. McComas. [1996].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  Petition for Review. California State Supreme Court. David S rand, Esq., Donald T. Ramsey, Esq., and Rosemary Springer, Esq. [1995].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  Petitioners' Consolidated Answer to Amicus Curiae Briefs of Cignal Healthcare of California, California Chamber of Commerce, and The Association for California Tort Reform. David S. Rand, Esq., Donald T. Ramsey, Esq., and Rosemary Springer, Esq. [1996].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  Petitioners' Opening Brief on the Merits [Application for Leave to File Amicus Curiae Brief in Support of Petitioners and Amicus Curiae Brief]. California State Supreme Court. [David S. Rand, Esq., Donald T. Ramsey, Esq., and Rosemary Springer, Esq.]. [1996].
- Engalla, et.al. v. Permanente Medical Group, Inc., et.al., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  Petitioners' Reply Brief on the Merits. California State Supreme Court. David S. Rand, Esq., Donald T. Ramsey, Esq., and Rosemary Springer, Esq. [1996].
- Fibreboard Paper Products v. NLRB, et.al., 1964 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  Brief for the United Steelworkers of America and its Affiliated Local Union 1304, East Bay Union of Machinists. U.S. Supreme Court 1964. David E. Feller, et.al.
- Fogle, et. al. v. United Steelworkers, et.al. (Box 18, Folder 23)
  Brief for Appellees. U.S. Court of Appeals, Third Circuit. David E. Feller, et.al.
- Fong Foo and Knupp v. U.S., 1960 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  Petition for a Writ of Certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the First Circuit. U.S. Supreme Court 1960. David E. Feller, Jerry D. Anker, and Samuel E. Agnoff.
- Garner and Garner, trading as Central Storage & Transfer v. Teamsters, et.al., 1953 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  Brief for the Congress of Industrial Organizations as Amicus Curiae. U.S. Supreme Court 1953. Arthur J. Goldberg and David E. Feller.
- Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee, CIO; E. J. Habshey v. Windsor, et.al., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  Reply Brief for Appellants. U.S. Supreme Court 1956. Arthur J. Goldberg, et.al.
- Gruenberg, Gladys W., Joyce M. Najita, and Dennis R. Nolan., 1997 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  The National Academy of Arbitrators: Fifty Years in the World of Work. Washington: BNA Books, The Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., 1997
- Guss D/B/A Photo Sound Products Manufacturing Company v. Utah Labor Relations Board., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  Brief for the United Steelworkers of America. U.S. Supreme Court 1956. Arthur J. Goldberg and David E. Feller
- Independent Petroleum Workers v. American Oil Company., 1963 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  Petition for a Writ of Certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the Seventh Circuit. U.S. Supreme Court 1963. William Belshaw, et.al.
- John Wiley & Sons v. Livingston, etc., 1963 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  Motion for Leave to File a Brief as Amicus Curiae and Brief for the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations as Amicus Curiae. U.S. Supreme Court 1963. J. Albert Woll, et.al.
- Labor Management Relations Act, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  Public Law 101. 80th Congress.
- Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959. (Box 18, Folder 32)
  Public Law 86-257. 86th Congress, S. 1555. September 14, 1959.
- Local 207 of International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers Union, et.al. v. Perko., 1962 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  Petitioners' Reply Brief. U.S. Supreme Court 1962. David E. Feller, et.al.
- Local 761, International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers v. NLRB, et.al., 1960 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  Reply Brief for United Steelworkers of America and International Chemical Workers Union, Amici Curiae. U.S. Supreme Court 1960. David E. Feller and Jerry D. Anker.
- Major League Baseball Players Association v. Garvey. (Box 18, Folder 35)
  Motion for Leave to File Brief Amicus Curiae and Brief Amicus Curiae of the National Academy of Arbitrators in Support of the Petition. U.S. Supreme Court. Washington, D.C.: Wilson-Epes, n.d. David E. Feller and John Kagel.
- Mamula v. United Steelworkers., 1964 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  Motion to Dismiss. U.S. Supreme Court 1964. David E. Feller, et.al.
- National Academy of Arbitrators. 2004 Membership Directory. (Box 18, Folder 37)
  [Cortland, NY?]: [National Academy of Arbitrators?], [2004?]
- National Academy of Arbitrators. Oral History Project, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  The Early Days of Labor Arbitration as Recalled by: G. Allan Dash, Jr., Sylvester Garrett, John Day Larkin, Harry H. Platt, Ralph T. Seward, William E. Simkin. 2nd printing Summer 1984. N.p.: National Academy of Arbitrators, 1982.
- Sawyer, Secretary of Commerce v. Youngstown Sheet and Tube, et. al., 1951 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  Brief for the United Steelworkers of America, CIO as Amicus Curiae. U.S. Supreme Court 1951. Arthur J. Goldberg, Thomas E. Harris, David E. Feller, Elliot Bredhoff.
- Textile Workers v. Lincoln Mills., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Brief for Petitioner. U.S. Supreme Court 1956. Benjamin Wyle, Arthur J. Goldberg, and David E. Feller.
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters, Local 2713 v. Bruce Hardwood Floors., 1997 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Motion for Leave to File Brief Amicus Curiae and Brief Amicus Curiae of the National Academy of Arbitrators in Support of the Petition. U.S. Supreme Court 1997. Washington, D.C.: Wilson-Epes, n.d. David E. Feller and George Nicolau.
- United Paperworkers and Ouachita, Local 654 v. Misco., 1986 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Brief of the National Academy of Arbitrators as Amicus Curiae in Support of Petitioners. U.S. Supreme Court 1986. Washington, D.C.: Wilson-Epes, n.d. David E. Feller and William P. Murphy.
- United Steelworkers and U.S. Steel., 1949 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Reply Brief of United Steelworkers of America on Duty of Companies to Bargain With the Union on Pensions. Steel Industry Board 1949. Arthur J. Goldberg, et. al.
- United Steelworkers v. American Manufacturing Co., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  1959- Goldberg, Feller & Bredhoff. N.p.: n.p., n.d.
- United Steelworkers v. American Manufacturing Company, United Steelworkers v. Warrier & Gulf, United Steelworkers v. Enterprise Wheel & Car., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  Brief for the Petitioner. U.S. Supreme Court 1959. Arthur J. Goldberg, et.al.
- United Steelworkers v. Enterprise Wheel and Car Corp., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- United Steelworkers v. R. H. Bouligny., 1964 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Petition for a Writ of Certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the Fourth Circuit. U.S. Supreme Court 1964. David E. Feller, et.al.
- United Steelworkers v. U.S.- Bredhoff, Elloit, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  1959. United States Supreme Court, October Term. N.p.: n.p., n.d.
- United Steelworkers v. U.S., et.al., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  On Writ of Certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit. U.S. Supreme Court 1959. Arthur J. Goldberg, et. al.
- United Steelworkers v. U.S., et.al., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  Petition for a Writ of Certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit. U.S. Supreme Court 1959. Arthur J. Goldberg, et.al.
- United Steelworkers v. Warrior & Gulf Navigation Co., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- United Steelworkers, Local 5895 v. NLRB and Carrier., 1962 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  Brief for Petitioners. U.S. Supreme Court 1962. David E. Feller, et.al.
- Vaca, et.al. v. Sipes., 1966 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  Brief for Petitioners. U.S. Supreme Court 1966. Henry A. Panethiere, et. al.
- Walker, et.al. v. North Carolina., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Petition for a Writ of Certiorari to the Supreme Court of North Carolina. U.S. Supreme Court 1959. David E. Feller, et. al.
- Wright v. Universal Maritime Service, et.al., 1997 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  Brief of the National Academy of Arbitrators as Amicus Curiae in Support of Petitioners. U.S. Supreme Court 1997. Washington, D.C.: Wilson-Epes, n.d. David E. Feller.